realtyjuggler.com 2019-05-19

# RealtyJuggler Real Estate Software Privacy Policy

## RealtyJuggler Privacy Policy

RealOrganized, Inc. respects and is committed to protecting your privacy. This document describes our Privacy Policy.

### Member Account Information

In order to use RealtyJuggler.com (Website), you (Member) must first complete the registration form. The information collected includes name, email address, mailing address and phone number. This information considered Member Account Information.

### Member Private Information

Our Members use RealOrganized, Inc. software and services to organize and store calendar, contacts, and deal information that they consider personal and private (Member Private Information). We respect the privacy of our members.

### Sharing of Information

We will not sell or rent Member Private Information or Member Account Information. Member Account Information and Member Private Information is only shared or used for the following purposes:

  * To communicate with our Members about their account including upgrade notifications, system status notifications, notifications of expiration of Membership, notifications of new features and services offered.
  * To provide customer service, feedback, training, and support to our members.
  * To administer and provide services to Member's account, including improvements to Website.
  * To Integrate with third party services such as MailChimp and Google when Member has activated these integrations.
  * Carry out core business operations such as accounting, filing taxes, and processing of credit card transactions.
  * Help detect, prevent, or investigate security incidents, fraud, and other abuse and/or misuse of our products and services.
  * To enforce compliance with our Terms & Conditions and applicable law.
  * To meet legal requirements, including complying with court orders, valid discovery requests, valid subpoenas, and other appropriate legal mechanisms.
  * To provide information to representatives and advisors, including attorneys and accountants, to help us comply with legal, accounting, or security requirements.
  * To prosecute and defend a court, arbitration, or similar legal proceeding.
  * To respond to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.
  * When a member first signs up for a free trial, they are asked how they heard about RealtyJuggler. As part of that referral program, member name may be provided to the source of the referral.

### Data Controllership

In the context of this Privacy Policy, we act as a data controller for the personal data that we process.

### Data Collected by Our Members

As you use Website, you may add, edit and import Member Private Information into our system you have collected. We have no direct relationship with any person other than you, and for that reason, you are responsible for making sure you have the appropriate permission to collect and process information about those individuals.

### Advertising

  * We do not serve pop-up or pop-under advertising.
  * We do not offer services that install hidden, ad-supported programs onto Members' computers.
  * We do not work with companies who engage in advertising through spyware, hidden ad-supported downloads or similar activities.

### Contact Us Form

In order to request sales and support, Members need to fill out a Contact Us form. The information collected includes name, phone number, and email address. This information is used exclusively to provides sales and support to the Member for the Website.

### Email & Phone

RealOrganized, Inc. may periodically call you (Member), send you SMS text messages, or send you emails regarding changes to the Website, the status of your membership, or as part of the sales & support process. RealOrganized, Inc. does not make available your Email address or phone number to third parties, except as required to complete a transaction.

### Your Ability to Edit Your Member Account Information

All personally identifiable information RealOrganized, Inc. collects on a Member is available for viewing and editing by our Member by accessing their profile. You can edit your Account Information at any time signing into RealtyJuggler.com and clicking on the account link in the upper-right hand corner of the screen. Member Private Information can be edited and deleted using the Website.

### Your Ability to Delete Your Account

You can delete your RealtyJuggler Account by contacting us via our online HelpDesk or via phone at: (970) 672-3467.

### Data Retention

RealOrganized, Inc. retains all sales and account information (including member Account Information) indefinitely. This information is used for accounting and tax purposes. Member Private Information is retained for a minimum of 60 days after a Membership has been cancelled or deactivated. This is to permit reactivation of the account by the Member at a later date. Member Private Information can be explicitly destroyed at any time by the Member by contacting RealOrganized, Inc. and requesting that your account be deleted. Deletion of an account is not reversible.

### Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the Member's hard drive containing information about the Member. By setting a cookie on Website, the Member would not have to log into our site more than once, thereby saving time while on Website. Cookies are required to use Website.

### Log Files

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track Member's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.

### Links

This website contains links to other sites. RealOrganized, Inc. is not responsible for the privacy practices other sites. All external links, when clicked on, will open a fresh window making clear that a new site is being accessed.

### A Note About Children

Website is not for individuals under the age of eighteen (18). RealOrganized, Inc. will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone we know to be under the age of eighteen (18).

### In the Event of Sale, Merger or Aquisition

If we are involved in a merger, acquisition, a sale of all or a substantial portion of our assets, or other similar sale transaction, your information will be transferred as part of that transaction.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

RealOrganized, Inc. may update this policy. If it does, it will post changes on its Website.

### Security

The security of your information is important to us. For this reason, we have created an extensive security program to ensure that your information is secure. You can read more about it here.

We invite you to contact us regarding this policy. You may contact us by mail at the following address:

RealOrganized, Inc.  
1226 W. Ash "C"   
Windsor, Colorado  
80550   
USA

You may contact us via our online HelpDesk or via phone at: (970) 672-3467

Date Last Modified: May 16, 2018
